many people draw this diagram when they
want to represent a four set Venn
diagram unfortunately this is not valid
can you figure out what's missing from
this diagram
but we can actually draw a valid four
set Venn diagram here's one possible way
to draw such a diagram we can check that
it's valid by finding all the regions
here's the regions for elements only in
a the ones only in B the ones only in C
and the ones only in D next are the
double intersection regions here's the
region for elements only in A and B this
one for those only in a and C this one
for those in A and D this one for those
in B and C only and in B and D only and
this one for those in C and D only next
we have the triple intersection regions
a b and c only a b and d only a c and d
only and b c and d only here's the
region for elements in all four sets and
here's the region for elements in none
of the four sets we've pictured all 16
possible regions so this is a valid Venn
diagram